<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
        <maintainer type="person">
                <email>sven.eden@prydeworx.com</email>
                <name>Sven Eden</name>
        </maintainer>
        <longdescription>Microsoft Teams for Linux is your chat-centered workspace in Office 365.
 Instantly access all your team’s content from a single place where messages, files, people and tools live together.
 This is a preview version, so bear with us while we do some fine-tuning.
 .
  ONE PLACE FOR YOUR TEAM’S FILES AND CONVERSATIONS:
  - Work with your team’s documents on the go
  - Move seamlessly across different team projects and topics
  - Mention individual team members or your entire team to get attention
 .
  STAY CONNECTED WITH PRIVATE AND TEAM CHAT:
  - Chat privately one-on-one or have instant group conversations
  - See real-time chat history on your favorite device and continue conversations started elsewhere
  - Chat with your entire team in dedicated channels
 .
  QUICKLY FIND WHAT YOU NEED:
  - Quickly search through your chats and team conversations
  - Find a contact through name or email address search
 .
  TAILOR YOUR WORKSPACE:
  - Include content and capabilities you need every day
  - Customize alerts to get notified when you get mentioned or get a message
  - Save important conversations to quickly access them later
 .
  SECURITY TEAMS TRUST:
  - Get the enterprise-level security and compliance you expect from Office 365
  - Enhanced security with multi-factor authentication
 .
 This app requires appropriate commercial Office 365 subscription.
 If you are not sure about your company’s subscription or the services you have access to, please contact your IT department.
 .
 By downloading this app, you agree to the license and privacy terms (see aka.ms/privacy).
 .
 To learn more, please visit aka.ms/microsoftteams</longdescription>
 <use>
        <flag name="system-ffmpeg">
                Use media-video/ffmpeg instead of the bundled lib. Might crash MS Teams!
        </flag>
        <flag name="system-mesa">
                Use media-libs/mesa instead of the bundled EGL and GLESv2 libs. Might crash MS Teams!
        </flag>
</use>
</pkgmetadata>
