<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
<herd>wine</herd>
<longdescription>
This build is a LGPL-part of WINE@Etersoft product prepared for
using commercial programs.
WINE Is Not Emulator. Wine is an Open Source implementation of the Windows
API on top of X and Unix.  Think of Wine as a compatibility layer for
running Windows programs. Wine does not require Microsoft Windows,
as it is a completely free alternative implementation of the Windows
API consisting of 100 percent LGPL code, however Wine can optionally
use native Windows DLLs if they are available. Wine provides both a
development toolkit for porting Windows source code to Unix as well as
a program loader, allowing many unmodified Windows programs to run on
x86-based Unixes, including Linux, FreeBSD, and Solaris.

It is still alpha level code; don't expect everything to work.
Check http://winehq.org.ru or http://winehq.org if you experience some problems.
Bug tracker: http://bugs.etersoft.ru

You can obtain commercial support of the product from Etersoft company:
wine@etersoft.ru
</longdescription> 
<longdescription lang="ru">
Данная сборка является свободной частью продукта WINE@Etersoft,
предназначенного для исполнения коммерческих Windows-программ.
WINE Не Является Эмулятором. Это альтернативная реализация API Windows
3.x и Win32. Wine предоставляет как инструментарий разработки (Winelib)
для переноса унаследованных исходных кодов из среды Windows в среду
Unix, так и программный загрузчик, позволяющий исполнять двоичный код, разработанный
для Windows 3.1/95/NT, в среде разных вариантов
Unix на платформе Intel. Wine не требует наличия Microsoft Windows,
поскольку это полностью альтернативная реализация, состоящая из полностью
свободного кода.

WINE всё ещё находится в стадии разработки, поэтому
не ожидайте, что всё будет работать.

Обращайтесь за дополнительной информацией на сайт http://winehq.org.ru
Система регистрации ошибок: http://bugs.etersoft.ru

При необходимости вы можете получить коммерческую поддержку данного продукта
в компании Etersoft или у её партнёров: wine@etersoft.ru
</longdescription> 
</pkgmetadata>
